Dan Dowling Cartoons
Dan Dowling Cartoons
1956-1966
Dowling, Dan, 1906-1993.
4.1 linear ft.
236 original editorial cartoons.
2643727
Biographical History
Dan Dowling (1906-1993) was an American editorial cartoonist who worked for the Omaha World Herald, the New York Herald Tribune and the Kansas City Star.
Born in O'Neill, Nebraska on November 16, 1906, Dan Dowling spent his childhood in Iowa. Dowling was influenced by the cartoons of Jay Norwood “Ding” Darling that appeared in the Des Moines Register and Leader and Carey Orr. Dowling attended the University of California-Berkeley from 1924 until 1928. Wanting to travel, Dowling joined a dance band and as the drummer got to travel the world. In 1931 he moved to Chicago where he briefly studied at the Academy of Fine Art before working as a police reporter.
In 1933 Dowling joined the Associated Press in New York as a retouch artist. Learning of an opening with the Omaha World Herald, Dowling moved back to the Midwest in 1937 to become the paper's cartoonist not having had any on the job cartooning experience. Dowling stayed in Omaha until World War II when he joined the infantry and served four years as a captain.
During the war, he submitted cartoons to the Omaha World Herald and the New York Herald Tribune. Dowling landed a job with the latter after the war and his editorial cartoons became syndicated in 1949. Dowling stayed at the New York Herald Tribune until the paper went out of business upon which he became the editorial cartoonist for the Kansas City Star where he stayed until his retirement.
Dowling won two Freedom Foundation Awards (1956 and 1960), a Christopher Award in 1960, a Sigma Chi Delta award (1960) and served as founding president of the American Association of Editorial Cartoonists from 1956 to 1958.
Dan Dowling retired to Carmel by the Sea, California and died of congestive heart failure on July 27, 1993.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Dan Dowling Cartoons consist of 235 original political cartoons from the years 1960-1966 that appeared in the New York Herald Tribune and were also syndicated. The cartoons are only marked with years. A few are completely undated. The majority of the cartoons are from 1966.
Dowling's portrayal of figures was typically less realistic and instead very caricaturesque. This can be seen in his treatment of President Lyndon Johnson as a cowboy hat wearing leader who regularly encounters cacti, clearly eliciting Johnson's Texas roots. Like other editorial cartoonists, Dowling visually represented the gamut of domestic and international political issues. For example one of the most heavily represented themes in this particular collection of Dowling cartoons is the economic effect of the Vietnam War. Few cartoons in the collection address issues local to New York.
The cartoons bear the copyright of the Publishers Newspaper Syndicate and the New York Herald Tribune. The cartoons were created on Glarco illustration board with India ink, brush, graphite and crayon as well as Benday screening.
Arrangement of the Collection
The cartoons are arranged in chronological order by year. Within each year the cartoons are arranged alphabetically by caption. A folder of completely undated cartoons is located at the end of the collection.
Related Material
has collections of over one hundred cartoonists. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Art -- Cartoonists; Dowling, Dan, 1906-1993.; New York herald tribune.; Publishers newspaper syndicate.; American wit and humor, Pictorial.; Caricatures and cartoons -- United States.; Cartoonists -- United States.; Editorial cartoons -- New York.; Editorial cartoons -- United States.; Inflation (Finance) -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Political cartoons.; Taxation -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; World politics -- 1945-1989 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Cartoons (humorous images); Editorial cartoons.; Cartoonists.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dan Dowling, 1966.
One cartoon, 1956, gift of Randy Rosen, 2012.
Inventory
- Cartoons, 236 items 20" x 14½ "
  - 1956
    - We have an agreement (Oversize 1, Folder 0)
  - 1960
    - And still they come (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
    - That's a grim procession (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
  - 1961
    - The big welcome (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
    - Doc, will you look at the next pasture? (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
    - The seed catalogue and the garden (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
    - What a mess to clean up (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
  - 1962
    - Is that a promise? (Oversize 1, Folder 3)
  - 1963
    - The bowlegged gate keeper (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - The bull calf is first to respond (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - The changing picture of Russia (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - Come home with us now! (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - The days of real sport (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - Fireworks display (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - In loving memory of the summer of '62 (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - It says to start turning on the heat (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - Let's have friendly relations for awhile! (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - Low tide (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    - Maybe we had better send for our winter underwear (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - Old boy friend reappears (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - Propaganda picture. (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - Red Riding Hood and the wolf (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - The tail that wags the dog (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - We've got to have more assurances! (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - Wrong pasture (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - You fellows mind if I slip in ahead? (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    - You sure you're in the right pasture? (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
  - 1964
    - Anybody thirsty? (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Back into the cockpit (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Bo Peep has lost a lot of sheep (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Boss, it's bound to be a campaign issue! (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Busy days of Gov. Scranton (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Delegate without credentials (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Everybody get set, here's the big one! (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Fight the war! (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Hail the 100th anniversary of communism! (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - Hello LBJ, it's Hubert. I've finished here, I'm on my way to — (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - His years in Congress (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
    - In the name of civil rights (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Is this a substitute for the traditional press conference? (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - It's really beginning to smell! (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - On the trail of the lonesome pine (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - One Memorial Day calls for another (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Our theory is, comfortable Communists are less dangerous! (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Out where the trade winds blow (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Remember, blood's thicker than water! (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Romance on the Nile (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - A short horse is soon curried (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - Sorry, we can't get that fellow to vacate the room! (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    - There's a lot more fish in the sea (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
    - This is your captain speaking! (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
    - The touring pro (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
    - Warden, you're sure he's locked up tight? (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
    - The wolf at the door (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
    - untitled (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
  - 1965
    - Cheering section (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - Do we start in where we left off? (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - The dogs bark and the caravans pass on. (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - Don't hesitate, take ahold! (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - Don't shoot, men, we might hit one of our allies! (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - Front row seat (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - His pyramid (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - I might come in if you all apologize! (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - I missed! (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - I sort of expected my own folks to meet me! (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
    - Obstetrical ward (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
    - Pause in the long weekend (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
    - Soon as he has a breather he'll be with you! (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
    - Still a lot of empty saddles in the old corral (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
    - Things are really cookin' (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
    - Turn back the clock (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
    - We've just completed the first 100 days! (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
  - 1966
    - The accompanist (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - All I know is our harbor's being mined! (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - All we can do is be patient and wait! (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - Another complaint to the head of the shop (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - Another teamster's convention (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - Anything else visible on the landscape? (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - As we see it, America is a long term paper tiger. (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - Attention all who follow Soviet affairs (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - The big drift (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - The big scalping (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - Boss, we've had some punctures! (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - The bridge builder (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - But let's make sure they don't! (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
    - Can Spring be far behind? (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Canadian beachhead (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Can't we shift into high gear? (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Careful, the old boy hasn't gone yet! (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Charting the course (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - The cliff dwellers (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Collision course again (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Coming in on the slow freight (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Congratulations, keep moving, next ... (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Could be a step in the right direction (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    - Did you ever see so much soup from one oyster? (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Did you have your antenna up around the voters? (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Dilemma (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Dull pruning shears (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Economic outlook (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Education in China (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Everybody out for "G" day (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Everybody relax (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Everything in firearms (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
    - Floating crap game (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - Fly in the ointment (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - Fondest hopes of little Ho (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - For the record I put in the routine threat on Viet Nam (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - The free ride (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - Front man in Indonesia (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - The great leap backward (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - Great society play ground (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - Grim struggle (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
    - Hands across the sea (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - Has the world changed much? (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - He doesn't want to take on anymore political problems. (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - He's beginning to drop some hints (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - The helping hand (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - Here we are again! (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - Here's a present for you! (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - Hope you counted the votes right (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - How to watch pro football (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - How we going to work him into the commercial? (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
    - I hope the rest of you just sit there and watch (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - I may start taking you boys seriously! (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - I understand it won't be 'til after elections (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - I understand we may run a slower second quarter (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - I want to file a complaint (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - I'll play all night. (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - I'll read you our program for '66. (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - Ice has started to form on the river (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - The idea is not to reward him! (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - The irresistable temptation (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - It's been hard on the furniture (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - It's a long high fly, the Administration is under it! (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - It's much trickier this year (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - It's time to make out a new list (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - I've been working my way toward the head of the line. (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    - Jack and the Bean Stalk (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Last few holes he's been picking up a gallery! (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Let him have a whif, then hit him again! (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Let's face it, we may lose some seats! (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Let's review the whole thing (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Let's start unscrambling (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Little left for those eating at the second table (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Maybe I should come out of retirement. (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Meet your roomates for the coming year (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - The more the merrier (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
    - Nation with the greatest productivity gains in history (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - News gets around (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - Nice idea, maybe we should do it again next year. (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - None of us are very happy with it. (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - Not a bad idea to stop off in the far west (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - Now comes the big test (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - One side everybody! (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - Peace initiative (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - Peculiar behavior of a chicken that loses its head (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - [Pre-election announcement] (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    - Race with the stork (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Reading between the lines (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Reap the whirlwind (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Ring down the asbestos curtain (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - See here, you keep your foot off the accelerator! (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Shall we move in for the kill? (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Shall we take a look now? (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - She barely got out of the door (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - SHHH, we must have absolute quiet. (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Ship Ahoy (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Skip the trick shooting! (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Slippery when wet (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    - Some cancellations on the old milk route (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - Somebody has to make the tackle (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - Someone is missing from the picture (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - Something happened to my sparkplugs (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - Spectator sport (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - Standard operating procedure (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - Start of a new era? (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
    - That's our united powerful ally (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - Then the rains came (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - There are two choices (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - There goes an odd couple (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - There was an old lady who lived in a shoe (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - There's a ray of sunshine (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - This happened after I left the farm (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - Triumph of national interests over ideology (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - Twenty third Communist Party Congress (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
    - Unsolved problem of the 20th Century (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - Vice-President Humphrey arrives with the gasoline (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - Wake up, I just had another brilliant idea! (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We don't find that the public is inconvenienced (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We don't know much about him, but he's been put in command (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We haven't had many good work days! (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We heard it many times before but let's hear it again (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We just ignore that! (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We might sit a little closer" (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We promise the service will be better! (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We sure have our lines in a mess (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We thought it over and we are of one mind (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We want to get our cause back (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    - We're bringing something into focus! (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - We're going to have to eat one of 'em (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - We're going to have to hold things up there (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - We're just skimming off some of the cream (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - We've gotten the message! (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - What are they trying to do? (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - What are the wild waves saying? (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - What a chance to be a hero (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - What happened? (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - What ideas you got on how peace can be attained? (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - When does the fun start? (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - While we're at it (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - White house pool (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - Whoopee (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - Who's burying who? (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    - Wide gap (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - Wish we could fight just one war at a time! (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - Wonder what the post-DeGaulle era will be like? (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - Wreck of the Hesperus (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - You can count on a very attentive audience (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - You can take your little precious home now (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - You do get the feeling they're living beyond their means (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - You want to go into consultation? (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    - You're just fiction (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
  - Undated cartoons, contains some unfinished sketches
    - Expand the great society! (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - The hate theme (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - Itching feet again (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - It's getting pretty low! (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - Pressure's been building up (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - Sanctuary (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - Somebody's going to have to do something (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - Sound the general alarm! (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - The stand-in (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - Visitors from the suburbs (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - What's the Viet Nam forecast today? (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - Who's my next appointment with?" (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
    - You all set for another landslide? (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
Index to cartoons
The following is a list of predominant people, places and subjects appearing in the editorial cartoons in this collection. The list is not exhaustive. Some subjects may require you to browse with alternative terms.
B= Box, F= Folder. For example: B1F1= Box 1 Folder 1. The links direct to the cartoon(s) about that topic.
Africa B2F6
Alabama B3F8
Appalachia B1F7
Asia B2F9 B3F7
auto industry B2F8 B3F1 B3F6 B3F8
automobile accidents B1F7 B2F8
Baker, Bobby B1F6 B1F7
Britain B1F4 B1F7 B1F7 B3F1 B3F8
Canada B2F4
Castro, Fidel B1F5 B1F7
Central Intelligence Agency B2F9
China B1F4 B1F7 B1F7 B2F1 B2F1 B2F1 B2F3 B2F4 B2F5 B2F5 B2F6 B2F6 B2F6 B2F8 B2F8 B2F9 B3F2 B3F4 B3F4 B3F5 B3F5 B3F6 B3F7
cities B3F2 B3F7
civil rights B1F6 B1F7 B2F8 B3F3 B3F5 B3F8
communism B1F2 B1F5 B1F6 B1F7 B2F2 B2F2 B2F3 B2F6 B2F8 B3F2 B3F8 B3F4 B3F4 B3F5
Congo B1F2
Congress B1F4 B1F4 B1F5 B1F5 B1F6 B1F6 B2F1 B2F1 B2F2 B2F3 B2F3 B2F4 B2F5 B2F6 B2F7 B3F1 B3F8 B3F2 B3F3 B3F6 B3F6 B3F7
crime B2F8
Cuba B1F2 B1F5 B3F8
de Gaulle, Charles B1F5 B1F8 B2F1 B2F3 B2F4 B2F5 B2F5 B2F7 B2F7 B3F8 B3F6 B3F7
Democratic National Convention B1F6
Democratic Party B1F1 B2F3 B2F9 B3F3 B3F3 B3F8
Dirksen, Everett B2F1
Douglas-Home, Alec B1F4
draft B3F1
economy B2F6 B2F7 B2F8 B3F4 B3F4
education B2F4 B2F5
Egypt B2F1
elections B1F6 B1F7 B1F7 B2F3 B2F4 B2F5 B2F6 B2F8 B2F8 B2F9 B2F9 B3F1 B3F1 B3F2 B3F4 B3F5 B3F5 B3F6 B3F8
Europe B2F5 B3F4
farming B1F2 B3F4
France B1F5 B2F3 B2F4 B3F7
freedom B3F5
Freeman, Orville B1F2
Germany B1F5
gold reserve B1F5 B3F8
Great Society B3F8 B2F1 B2F2 B2F4 B2F8 B2F9 B3F5 B3F7
Ho Chi Minh B2F6 B2F8 B3F2
Hoffa, Jimmy B2F3
holidays B2F2 B3F1 B3F5
Humphrey, Hubert B1F6 B2F9 B3F2 B3F2 B3F5
India B2F1
Indonesia B2F6
inflation B1F8 B2F4 B2F5 B2F6 B2F6 B2F7 B2F7 B2F8 B2F8 B2F9 B3F2 B3F2 B3F2 B3F3 B3F3 B3F4 B3F4 B3F5 B3F5 B3F6 B3F6 B2F5 B3F8 B3F8
Johnson, Lyndon Baines B1F6 B1F6 B1F6 B1F7 B1F8 B1F8 B2F1 B2F2 B2F2 B2F3 B2F4 B2F5 B2F8 B2F8 B2F9 B3F1 B3F2 B3F3 B3F4 B3F4 B3F6
Kennedy, Robert F. B2F4 B2F9 B3F2 B3F2 B3F4
Korea B2F6
Ky, Nguyen Cao B2F5
labor B2F7 B3F3 B3F5 B3F5
Latin America B1F5 B3F8 B3F7
Lenin, Vladimir B3F4
Lindsay, John B2F2
Manila Summit Conference B3F7
Marx, Karl B1F6
McNamara, Robert B2F3 B3F8
Meany, George B3F3
Medicare B2F9 B3F2 B3F7
Memorial Day B1F7 B2F8
military B1F8
Nasser, Gamal Abdel B2F1
nature B2F3
New York B1F8
New York City B2F2 B3F2 B3F8 B3F8
nuclear weapons B1F4 B2F4 B2F5
Pakistan B2F1
peace B2F1 B2F2 B3F1 B3F6 B3F7
Poland B1F0
politics B2F3 B2F7
poverty B1F8
Powell, Adam Clayton B3F6
presidential appointments B1F1 B2F2
prices B2F5 B2F6 B2F8 B3F3 B3F7
prisoners of war B2F2
racism B3F8
railroad industry B1F5
Republican Party B3F4 B3F6
Reuther, Walter B2F8
Rockefeller, Nelson B1F8
Rusk, Dean B1F2
Russia B1F0 B1F4 B2F3 B2F3 B2F7 B3F2 B3F3 B3F6
Scranton, William B1F6
Soviet Union B1F2 B1F4 B1F7 B1F7 B2F3 B2F3 B2F4 B2F4 B2F6 B2F7 B2F7 B2F8 B3F2 B3F4 B3F5 B3F5
space exploration B2F7
sports B3F5
Stevenson, Adlai E. B1F2
stock market B1F4 B2F7 B3F4 B3F6
strikes B1F5 B2F7 B3F2 B3F5
Sukarno B2F6 B3F1
taxes B1F2 B1F3 B1F4 B1F4 B1F4 B1F6 B2F3 B2F3 B2F5 B2F6 B2F6 B2F7 B2F7 B2F8 B2F8 B2F8 B2F9 B3F4 B3F5 B3F6 B3F6 B3F7 B3F8
television B1F7
U.S. Mail B2F9 B3F1
unions B2F7 B3F1 B3F2
United Nations B2F1
Vietnam War B1F5 B3F8 B1F7 B2F1 B2F1 B2F1 B2F1 B2F2 B2F3 B2F3 B2F3 B2F3 B2F4 B2F4 B2F5 B2F5 B2F6 B2F6 B2F6 B2F8 B2F9 B3F2 B3F2 B3F4 B3F5 B3F6 B3F6 B3F7 B3F8
violence B2F8 B3F5
war B2F1 B2F9
War on Poverty B1F7 B3F6
weather B1F4 B1F7 B2F4
Wilson, Harold B3F1 B3F8
Zedong, Mao B2F5